pixnio.com 2018-09-07

# Privacy policy

## **The privacy of our visitors is important to us.**

 **What personal data we collect and what rights you have over your data?**

Personally-identifiable information collected on this website is gathered on our “[contact](https://pixnio.com/contact-us "contact")” page, where fields are provided so that you can provide your name, email address. We collect this information so that we can respond to message you send to us via that form. We can have your info only if you send it to us via email. You can also request that we erase any personal data that you send us via our “contact” page (exept any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes).

If you register on our website, we store the personal information you provide in your user profile (if any), you can see, edit, or delete your personal information at any time, except you cannot change username. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you (exept any data we are obliged to keep).

 **Comments**

If visitor leave comments on our site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser info to help spam detection. Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service. You can request that we erase any personal data in any comments, or any comments posted by you (exept any data we are obliged to keep).

 **Media**

Visitors of our site can upload media to site, if any media is uploaded by visotor and if we publish it (if is suitable for bublishing) it will be publicly accessible.  
Please note that if you upload images to our website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded GPS info (EXIF GPS info), because we may show that info with image, also visitors of website can download and extract GPS location where image is taken. That info can be useful, and can provide more info about picture, but think about that before uploading images which contain GPS info. Media you upload may be checked through an automated detection service. You can request that we erase any media that represents any personal data about you (exept any data we are obliged to keep).

 **Anonymous information collected on this website**

We record anonymous data. Most of the information that we collect from this website is anonymous information, such as the pages you visit. Other anonymous data we may collect might include the name of your internet service provider, the website that you used to link to our site, the websites that you visit from our site, and your IP address. The data is used for statistical purposes, but you, as the individual user, remain anonymous. We use this anonymous information to help improve the content of this site and to compile aggregate statistics about individuals using our site for internal market research purposes.

 **Log files**

Like many other web sites, this too make use of log files. The information inside the log files may includes internet protocol addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider, date / time stamp, referring / exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

 **Cookies and web beacons**

This site use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

If you leave a comment on our website you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies, these cookies will last for one year.

If you registered an account and you log in to our site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. Cookie contains no personal data, also it is discarded when you close your browser. If you log in to our website we will also set up several cookies to save your login info. This login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year, if you select “Remember Me“, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

 **Website analytics and ads**

We use third-party analytics services (Google Analytics) to get statistics about our website, such as number of visitor, origin and behaviour. Information we gather from analytics are anonymous and we cannot identify a particular visitors of our website.  
We use third-party advertising services (AdSense) to serve ads on our website. Our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on this site send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. This site has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party services for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Our privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the web browsers respective websites. Please note that if you disable browser cookies, most website features will work, but you will be unable to register / login on website and therefore unable to upload / share your media files, post commernts.

 **How do we protect information and media on website?**

We use the industry-standard SSL protocol to ensure that communication to / from our website is encrypted and as secure as possible. To be sure that you are communicate with our site, our URL address is: https://pixnio.com  
We scan our website on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities to make visits to our website safe.  
Website provide only articles, media and information. We do not ask for personal or private information like credit card numbers.  
We use regular malware scanning.

 **Contact**

If you have any question or privacy-specific concerns please do not hesitate to contact us, you can do it via “[contact](https://pixnio.com/contact-us "contact")” page.

You consent to our privacy policy if you continue to use this website.
